

### About Me

Hello, I am Julie. I'm a Full-Stack Developer and programmer. I have 4 years of experience in development sector. completed too many projects and codes, I have archive some technologies in this sector like -HTML,CSS, Javascript, Nodejs, Python etc

## Contact

- +8801302661227
- ghsjulian@gmail.com
- wwe.ghs.rf.gd
- 3222, Sylhet, Maulovibazar, Komolgonj

# **登 Skills**

- Web Design
- Web Development
- Website Developer
- SEO
- Marketing
- Programmer & Freelancer

# **Language**

- English
- Bangla
- Hindi

# **Ghs Julian**

Web Developer & Designer



## Education

2019-2021

**HSC BM(HIGHER SECONDARY)** 

**Business Management** 4.50

2021-2023

**NATIONAL UNIVERSITY** 

BA Honours (English) 4.00



## **Experience**

(2022 - 2023)

### FRONT-END WEB DESIGNER

Self Learning Projects

- create more than 20+ projects
- complete a lot of complicated work

(2021 - 2023)

### **BACKEND DEVELOPER**

PHP & MySQL

- create more than 10+ projects
- complete a lot of complicated work
- completed restful API with PHP

(2022 - 2022)

### **PYTHON DEVELOPER**

Python

• create more than 5+ tools for ethical works